picture?
え?
what happened?
どうしたの?
picture?
え?
what happened?
どうしたの?
It snapped.
ピッて言った
Is it okay to take pictures?
撮っちゃダメなの?
撮っちゃダメですか?
I took a picture.
撮りました
Are you taking pictures?
撮ってます?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
That's amazing, those abs.
すごいね、腹筋ね
Can I see your breasts?
おっぱい見ていいですか?
I thought I'd like to see some breasts.
おっぱいちょっと見たいなと思って
What should I do?
どうすればいいですか?
Can I have your picture taken?
撮ってもらっていいですか?
Stand up for a moment.
ちょっと 立ってよ
What an amazing sexy pose.
なんかすごいセクシーポーズさん
Amazing sexy pose?
すごいセクシーポーズ?
I did it again.
もう一回やったよ
Please don't take pictures.
撮らないでください
Like running and sticking out?
走り突き出しみたいな?
Is this how you feel?
こういう気持ち?
It's so naughty.
すっごいやらしい
delicious?
おいしい?
amazing.
すごい
That's naughty.
やらしい
やらしいですね
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい
Do it manually.
手動かしてよ
I'll put it out.
出すよ
I'll give you a lot.
いっぱい出すよ
Oh, I put it out.
ああ、出しちゃった
That's because it gets intense all of a sudden.
急 に激しくするからだよ
How does it feel?
どんな感じする?
nice.
いいね